<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Research on Akablog Hugo Theme</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/research/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Research on Akablog Hugo Theme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>id-id</language>
    <copyright>© {year} Nama Anda atau Nama Blog Anda. Hak Cipta Dilindungi.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How collaboration makes us better designers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/08-collaboration-better-designers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/08-collaboration-better-designers/</guid>
      <description>Design is rarely a solo endeavor. Effective collaboration with developers, product managers, and other stakeholders is key to creating successful products. Learn strategies for fostering a collaborative environment and improving your teamwork skills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Wireframing?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/07-what-is-wireframing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/07-what-is-wireframing/</guid>
      <description>Wireframing is a critical step in the design process, allowing you to outline the structure and functionality of a digital product before diving into visual details. This guide covers the basics, benefits, and best practices for creating effective wireframes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PM mental models</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/06-pm-mental-models/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/06-pm-mental-models/</guid>
      <description>Effective Product Managers leverage a toolkit of mental models to navigate complex decisions and drive product strategy. Explore key frameworks like Jobs-to-be-Done, Cynefin, and the Kano Model to enhance your problem-solving and decision-making skills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrating to Linear 101</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/02-migrating-to-linear-101/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/02-migrating-to-linear-101/</guid>
      <description>Migrating your project management to a new tool like Linear can be a game-changer for productivity. This guide walks you through the essential steps, from planning and data import to team onboarding and customization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UX review presentations</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/01-ux-review-presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/01-ux-review-presentations/</guid>
      <description>As a UX designer or researcher, you spend countless hours delving into problems, understanding users, and identifying opportunities. But all that brilliant insight won&amp;rsquo;t mean much if it&amp;rsquo;s not communicated effectively. This is where UX review presentations play a crucial role. They&amp;rsquo;re not just reports; they&amp;rsquo;re an opportunity to inspire action and drive data-backed decisions.&#xA;Why UX Review Presentations Matter Imagine you&amp;rsquo;ve just completed a thorough UX audit of a product.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
