<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Akablog Hugo Theme</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Akablog Hugo Theme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>id-id</language>
    <copyright>© {year} Nama Anda atau Nama Blog Anda. Hak Cipta Dilindungi.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 10:05:00 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dokumentasi Tema Akablog</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/documentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 10:05:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/documentation/</guid>
      <description>Tema Akablog Hugo Tema blog yang dibuat menggunakan generator situs statis Hugo, di-styling dengan framework CSS Tailwind, dan beberapa aspek pengembangannya dibantu oleh Gemini AI.&#xA;Fitur Utama Desain Modern &amp;amp; Responsif: Tampilan yang bersih, minimalis, dan menyesuaikan diri dengan berbagai ukuran layar (desktop, tablet, mobile). Mode Terang &amp;amp; Gelap: Pilihan tema terang dan gelap yang dapat diubah oleh pengguna dan preferensinya akan disimpan. Daftar Postingan dengan Paginasi: Navigasi yang mudah antar halaman daftar postingan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Podcast: Creating a better CX Community</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/10-podcast-cx-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/10-podcast-cx-community/</guid>
      <description>Building a thriving customer experience (CX) community can provide invaluable feedback and foster brand loyalty. This podcast episode explores practical tips and strategies for launching, engaging, and growing a successful CX community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our top 10 Javascript frameworks to use</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/09-top-10-js-frameworks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/09-top-10-js-frameworks/</guid>
      <description>The JavaScript ecosystem is vast and ever-evolving. This overview highlights ten popular JavaScript frameworks, comparing their strengths, use cases, and learning curves to help you choose the right tool for your next project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How collaboration makes us better designers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/08-collaboration-better-designers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/08-collaboration-better-designers/</guid>
      <description>Design is rarely a solo endeavor. Effective collaboration with developers, product managers, and other stakeholders is key to creating successful products. Learn strategies for fostering a collaborative environment and improving your teamwork skills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Wireframing?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/07-what-is-wireframing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/07-what-is-wireframing/</guid>
      <description>Wireframing is a critical step in the design process, allowing you to outline the structure and functionality of a digital product before diving into visual details. This guide covers the basics, benefits, and best practices for creating effective wireframes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PM mental models</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/06-pm-mental-models/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/06-pm-mental-models/</guid>
      <description>Effective Product Managers leverage a toolkit of mental models to navigate complex decisions and drive product strategy. Explore key frameworks like Jobs-to-be-Done, Cynefin, and the Kano Model to enhance your problem-solving and decision-making skills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Walsh leadership lessons</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/05-bill-walsh-leadership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/05-bill-walsh-leadership/</guid>
      <description>Bill Walsh&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Standard of Performance&amp;rdquo; philosophy offers timeless leadership lessons applicable far beyond the football field. Discover how his principles of meticulous preparation, clear communication, and fostering a culture of excellence can elevate any team or organization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grid system for better Design User Interface</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/04-grid-system-for-better-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/04-grid-system-for-better-design/</guid>
      <description>Grid systems provide a foundational structure for consistent and harmonious web design. Understand the principles behind grid layouts and how to apply them effectively to improve visual hierarchy, alignment, and user experience across your interfaces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building your API Stack</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/03-building-your-api-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/03-building-your-api-stack/</guid>
      <description>Choosing the right tools for your API stack is crucial for development efficiency and scalability. Explore popular options for API design, development, testing, and monitoring to build a robust and maintainable system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrating to Linear 101</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/02-migrating-to-linear-101/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/02-migrating-to-linear-101/</guid>
      <description>Migrating your project management to a new tool like Linear can be a game-changer for productivity. This guide walks you through the essential steps, from planning and data import to team onboarding and customization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UX review presentations</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/01-ux-review-presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/01-ux-review-presentations/</guid>
      <description>As a UX designer or researcher, you spend countless hours delving into problems, understanding users, and identifying opportunities. But all that brilliant insight won&amp;rsquo;t mean much if it&amp;rsquo;s not communicated effectively. This is where UX review presentations play a crucial role. They&amp;rsquo;re not just reports; they&amp;rsquo;re an opportunity to inspire action and drive data-backed decisions.&#xA;Why UX Review Presentations Matter Imagine you&amp;rsquo;ve just completed a thorough UX audit of a product.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
