<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Akablog Hugo Theme</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Akablog Hugo Theme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>id-id</language>
    <copyright>© {year} Nama Anda atau Nama Blog Anda. Hak Cipta Dilindungi.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 10:05:00 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dokumentasi Tema Akablog</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/documentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 10:05:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/documentation/</guid>
      <description>Tema Akablog Hugo Tema blog yang dibuat menggunakan generator situs statis Hugo, di-styling dengan framework CSS Tailwind, dan beberapa aspek pengembangannya dibantu oleh Gemini AI.&#xA;Fitur Utama Desain Modern &amp;amp; Responsif: Tampilan yang bersih, minimalis, dan menyesuaikan diri dengan berbagai ukuran layar (desktop, tablet, mobile). Mode Terang &amp;amp; Gelap: Pilihan tema terang dan gelap yang dapat diubah oleh pengguna dan preferensinya akan disimpan. Daftar Postingan dengan Paginasi: Navigasi yang mudah antar halaman daftar postingan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Podcast: Creating a better CX Community</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/10-podcast-cx-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/10-podcast-cx-community/</guid>
      <description>🎧 Podcast: Building Bridges – Creating a Better CX Community (Intro Music: Upbeat, warm, and inviting)&#xA;Host: Welcome back to &amp;ldquo;The Customer-Centric Voice,&amp;rdquo; the podcast dedicated to all things customer experience! I&amp;rsquo;m your host, [Your Name], and today, we&amp;rsquo;re diving into a topic close to my heart: how do we create a better, more supportive, and impactful CX community?&#xA;We all know CX professionals are passionate, innovative, and constantly striving to make things better for customers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>top 10 Javascript frameworks to use</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/09-top-10-js-frameworks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/09-top-10-js-frameworks/</guid>
      <description>The JavaScript ecosystem is a vibrant, ever-evolving landscape. New frameworks and libraries emerge constantly, while established ones continue to innovate. For developers, choosing the right framework for a project can be a daunting, yet crucial, decision.&#xA;As we stand in 2025, several JavaScript frameworks have cemented their positions as industry leaders, offering powerful features, robust communities, and excellent performance for a wide range of applications. This list highlights the Top 10 JavaScript Frameworks you should consider for your next project, spanning both frontend and backend development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How collaboration makes us better designers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/08-collaboration-better-designers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/08-collaboration-better-designers/</guid>
      <description>In the world of design, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to picture the lone genius, toiling away in isolation, only to emerge with a brilliant, fully-formed masterpiece. While individual talent is undeniable, the reality is that collaboration is the secret ingredient that truly elevates design, making us better designers in the process.&#xA;Design, especially in complex digital products and services, is rarely a solitary endeavor. It&amp;rsquo;s a multidisciplinary dance, a symphony of ideas where diverse perspectives converge to create something far greater than any one person could achieve alone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Wireframing?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/07-what-is-wireframing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/07-what-is-wireframing/</guid>
      <description>Wireframing is a critical step in the design process, allowing you to outline the structure and functionality of a digital product before diving into visual details. This guide covers the basics, benefits, and best practices for creating effective wireframes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PM mental models</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/06-pm-mental-models/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/06-pm-mental-models/</guid>
      <description>Effective Product Managers leverage a toolkit of mental models to navigate complex decisions and drive product strategy. Explore key frameworks like Jobs-to-be-Done, Cynefin, and the Kano Model to enhance your problem-solving and decision-making skills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Walsh leadership lessons</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/05-bill-walsh-leadership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/05-bill-walsh-leadership/</guid>
      <description>Bill Walsh&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Standard of Performance&amp;rdquo; philosophy offers timeless leadership lessons applicable far beyond the football field. Discover how his principles of meticulous preparation, clear communication, and fostering a culture of excellence can elevate any team or organization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grid system for better Design User Interface</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/04-grid-system-for-better-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/04-grid-system-for-better-design/</guid>
      <description>Grid systems provide a foundational structure for consistent and harmonious web design. Understand the principles behind grid layouts and how to apply them effectively to improve visual hierarchy, alignment, and user experience across your interfaces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building your API Stack</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/03-building-your-api-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/03-building-your-api-stack/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s interconnected digital landscape, APIs (Application Programming Interfaces) are the backbone of almost every successful software product. From mobile apps talking to backend servers, to microservices communicating with each other, to integrating with third-party platforms, a well-designed and robust API stack is non-negotiable.&#xA;But what exactly goes into &amp;ldquo;building an API stack&amp;rdquo;? It&amp;rsquo;s more than just writing endpoints. It encompasses the entire ecosystem of tools, technologies, and practices that enable seamless data exchange and functionality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrating to Linear 101</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/02-migrating-to-linear-101/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/02-migrating-to-linear-101/</guid>
      <description>So, your team&amp;rsquo;s decided to make the switch to Linear? Great choice! Linear has rapidly become a favorite for product and engineering teams thanks to its speed, clean interface, and focus on developer experience. But, like any migration, moving your existing workflows and data can feel a bit daunting.&#xA;Don&amp;rsquo;t sweat it. This guide, &amp;ldquo;Migrating to Linear 101,&amp;rdquo; will walk you through the essential steps to ensure a smooth transition. We&amp;rsquo;ll cover everything from preparation to data import, getting your team onboard, and making the most of Linear&amp;rsquo;s powerful features.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UX review presentations</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/01-ux-review-presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/01-ux-review-presentations/</guid>
      <description>As a UX designer or researcher, you spend countless hours delving into problems, understanding users, and identifying opportunities. But all that brilliant insight won&amp;rsquo;t mean much if it&amp;rsquo;s not communicated effectively. This is where UX review presentations play a crucial role. They&amp;rsquo;re not just reports; they&amp;rsquo;re an opportunity to inspire action and drive data-backed decisions.&#xA;Why UX Review Presentations Matter Imagine you&amp;rsquo;ve just completed a thorough UX audit of a product.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
